{
    "subject": "resource/Athletics_at_the_1952_Summer_Olympics_\u2013_Men's_4_\u00d7_100_metres_relay",
    "predicate": "ontology/bronzeMedalist",
    "object": "resource/G\u00e9za_Varasdi",
    "human_readable": "G\u00e9za Varasdi won a bronze medal in the men's 4x100 meters relay at the 1952 Summer Olympics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9855090975761414,
            "question": "Who won a bronze medal in the men's 4x100 meters relay at the 1952 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9644393920898438,
            "question": "Name the athlete who won a bronze medal in the men's 4x100 meters relay."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9545505046844482,
            "question": "Which event did G\u00e9za Varasdi compete in at the 1952 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9506367444992065,
            "question": "Was G\u00e9za Varasdi part of a team at the 1952 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.932068407535553,
            "question": "What sport did G\u00e9za Varasdi compete in at the 1952 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9026939868927002,
            "question": "In what year did G\u00e9za Varasdi win his Olympic medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.796825647354126,
            "question": "What type of relay did G\u00e9za Varasdi compete in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7917869091033936,
            "question": "What color medal did G\u00e9za Varasdi win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7410616874694824,
            "question": "What kind of Olympics did G\u00e9za Varasdi participate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6347726583480835,
            "question": "Did G\u00e9za Varasdi win gold or silver at the Olympics?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=G\u00e9za Varasdi won a bronze medal in the men's 4x100 meters relay at the 1952 Summer Olympics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6337_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of Olympics did G\u00e9za Varasdi participate in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6337_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What color medal did G\u00e9za Varasdi win?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6337_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of relay did G\u00e9za Varasdi compete in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6337_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6337_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6337_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6337_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6337_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6337_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6337_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6337_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6337_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6337_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6337_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to document 37.txt, G\u00e9za Varasdi was part of a fabled quartet called the \"lightning four\" that won bronze behind the United States and Soviet Union with a time of 40.5sec at the Helsinki 1952 Olympics in the men's 4x100m relay event. This information supports the triple statement, confirming that G\u00e9za Varasdi indeed won a bronze medal in the men's 4x100 meters relay at the 1952 Summer Olympics."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context mentions that Zar\u00e1ndi, who was part of the Hungarian quartet with G\u00e9za Varasdi, won a bronze medal in the men's 4x100 meters relay at the Helsinki 1952 Olympics. Therefore, the statement that G\u00e9za Varasdi won a bronze medal in this event is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states that the \"lightning four\" quartet, which included G\u00e9za Varasdi, won bronze at the Helsinki 1952 Olympics.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}